[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After harvesting, coffee beans must be dried.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these musicians became the first US musical group ever to perform in North Korea?", "correct_answer": "The New York Philharmonic Orchestra", "incorrect_answers": ["The Black Eyed Peas", "The Helen Henderson Choir of Victory Baptist Church", "Linkin Park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mars has the tallest known mountain in the Solar System. What is its name?", "correct_answer": "Olympus Mons", "incorrect_answers": ["Arsia Mons", "Syrtis Major", "Tharsis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which song was Billy Joels first US Top Ten Hit?", "correct_answer": "Just the Way You Are", "incorrect_answers": ["Moivin Out", "Piano Man", "Shes  Got A Way"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How big was the first telephone book?", "correct_answer": "1 page", "incorrect_answers": ["50 pages", "100 pages", "10 pages"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does the Sundance Kid not jump off the cliff into the water to escape inevitable death in the western film Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid?", "correct_answer": "He cant swim.", "incorrect_answers": ["Hes afraid of heights.", "He hates being wet.", "Hes allergic to water."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is used to designate a hurricanes calm, low-pressure center around which winds of high velocity spin?", "correct_answer": "Eye", "incorrect_answers": ["Outer rim", "Eye wall", "Rain bands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do Oscar Robertson (ex-NBA All-Star) and Roy Orbison (the great singer/songwriter) have in common?", "correct_answer": "The same nickname", "incorrect_answers": ["The same birthplace", "The same birthdate", "The same wife"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Camp Rock, Tess is the daughter of the famous singer T.J. Tyler.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the result of the gravitational pull from the moon and sun.", "correct_answer": "Tides", "incorrect_answers": ["Migration of certain species of whales", "Shoreline", "Waves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Major League the Cleveland Indians are controlled by the former-showgirl widow of the recently deceased owner. Who was the owner that passed away on their honeymoon?", "correct_answer": "Donald Phelps", "incorrect_answers": ["Lou Phelps", "Charlie Phelps", "Roger Phelps"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The exploration of the Loch Ness Monster is related to which field of study?", "correct_answer": "Cryptozoology", "incorrect_answers": ["Phycology", "Ornithology", "Mycology"]}]